<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Ariel</family_id>
<family_name>ARIEL</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>FITNESS ADVENTURE</experience>
<description>The Ariel is a true hybrid. With geometry inspired by fun and fitness, including a low standover height, multiple lightweight frame options, and off-road capable fork, it’s your all-access pass to pavement, dirt, and everything in between. With fender and rack mounts, the versatile Ariel turns from local trail explorer to fast-rolling, commuting machine in the blink of an eye.</description></family_experience>
<headline>ALL OUT. ANYWHERE.</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Confidence-inspiring ride and best out-of-the-box fit courtesy of Women’s Fitness Geometry, low standover, and stable wheelbase</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>True hybrid versatility thanks to fast-rolling 700c wheels and off-road capable forks and components</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Great efficiency and wide-ranging appeal thanks to multiple lightweight frame options including A1 and M4 alloy models in double diamond and step-through options</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Commuters can easily outfit their bikes with racks, fenders, and kickstands for maximum utility</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Optimised performance with disc brakes on higher spec models (all models are disc compatible)</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>FENDER/RACK/KICKSTAND COMPATIBLE</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: All frame options feature fully integrated fender, rack, and kickstand mounts.</what1>
<why1>WHY: To ensure maximum versatility with minimal effort.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Mounting braze-ons are integrated into the frames in easy-to-reach locations. Rider can choose which and how many accessories to mount according to her needs. And with the easy accessibility, these can quickly be added/removed depending on the ride of the day.</how1>
<feature2>Women’s M4 or A1 Premium Aluminium Frames</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Fully butted M4 or A1 Premium Aluminium frames featuring Women’s Fitness Geometry, smooth welds, and full fender/rack compatibility. Extra small and step-through models available.</what2>
<why2>WHY: To create the lightest weight, most versatile, and best fitting all-road bike for women.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Our engineers optimise frame tube shapes and diameters specifically for women to maximise compliance, handling, and fit. With each frame designed from the ground up, we created a smaller size (XS) and step-through model while improving standover and geometry on all other sizes to make the Ariel accessible to the widest range of riders.</how2>
<feature3>Women’s Components</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Women’s Body Geometry Riva saddle, women’s Body Geometry XCT grips, and size-specific crank lengths.</what3>
<why3>WHY: To ensure that female riders get the most comfort and best fit from every contact point.</why3>
<how3>HOW: Through pressure mapping studies with Dr. Roger Minkow, we optimise the foam densities and cutouts in our saddles to relieve soft tissue discomfort, and our grips are designed with varying thickness to anatomically contour to the hands. Crank lengths are chosen based on female rider sizes.</how3>
<feature4>CUSTOM-TUNED SUSPENSION FORK</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Fully functioning, damped, 60/50mm-travel adjustable forks with size-specific spring weights, lockout on all models, and custom fork crown.</what4>
<why4>WHY: Better control and off-road handling for a more predictable and comfortable ride.</why4>
<how4>HOW: The fork is tuned for the average weight range of female riders. Combined with improved top-out, which reduces harsh rebounds, this creates a buttery-smooth ride and full travel range for every rider. With a lockout, riders gain more efficiency on surface streets or gentle trails.</how4></features>
<images><image href="file:///92E2-41_ARIEL_COMP DISC_BLK GRN WHT.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Ariel1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Ariel2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Ariel3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>
