<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Crave</family_id>
<family_name>CRAVE</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>PERFORMANCE HARDTAIL</experience>
<description>For riders who want to begin to compete at a higher level, on a race-proven 29-inch hardtail that packs huge performance and value, Crave is an ideal rig. These riders are becoming more dedicated racers and will benefit from Crave’s lightweight and efficient frame equipped with race-capable geometry, quality air-sprung suspension forks, and lightweight 29-inch wheelsets.</description></family_experience>
<headline>RACE-PROVEN PERFORMANCE</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Race-level performance and amazing value</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Brand-new, highly efficient, fully butted, and lightweight M4 alloy frame with shaped seatstays for increased vertical compliance</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Smoother ride and lighter weight through tapered seat tube, bridge-less seatstays and 27.2mm seatpost, which allows more compliance and minimises excess material</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Ultra-quick acceleration and handling with race-capable geometry and tapered 1-1/8” to 1-1/2” headtube</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>High-end performance and light weight, thanks to a 100mm-travel, air-sprung fork with tapered alloy steerer, magnesium lowers, and rebound adjust</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>M4 Premium Aluminium Frame</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: New fully manipulated M4 alloy frame with XC 29er-specific geo, plus tapered head and seat tubes, and shaped seatstays.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Keeps the bike stiff and efficient, with super-quick handling and acceleration, while allowing for a smooth, compliant ride.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Like all our 29er geos, this one features short chainstays and a longer toptube to optimise performance with the larger wheels. The new Crave frame provides 12.5% more vertical compliance through redesigned seatstay shaping. For maximum torsional rigidity and snappy handling, the headtube tapers from 1-1/8” to 1-1/2” at the crown. The Crave seat tube utilises a 27.2mm post at the top, but widens at the bottom bracket for a compliant ride and stiff crank interface.</how1>
<feature2>Lightweight 29-inch wheelsets</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Race-capable, lightweight alloy wheelsets on every model.</what2>
<why2>WHY: To provide quicker handling and improved durability and efficiency.</why2>
<how2>HOW: By using less material in low stress areas, which reduces rotational weight and requires less effort from the rider to turn the wheels.</how2>
<feature3>Air-sprung Fork w/ tapered steerer</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Lightweight, air-sprung fork with magnesium lowers and a tapered alloy steerer, plus hydraulic lockout and damping.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Reduces weight and improves bump absorption, steering precision, and tunability.</why3>
<how3>HOW: Air-sprung forks are lighter than coil-sprung versions, and allow the rider to tune the spring rate to their specific weight and riding style. Damping provides more controlled suspension movement.</how3></features>
<image href="file:///91714-10_CRAVE_PRO 29_BLK CHAR RKTRED.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Crave1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Crave2.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>