<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14CrossTrail</family_id>
<family_name>CROSSTRAIL</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>Fitness Adventure</experience>
<description>The Crosstrail is a light and fast fitness machine that handles a wide range of terrain. It’s the perfect setup for a weekend adventure ride on gravel trails, fire roads, paved pathways and everything in between. It’s your workout companion, but also offers great versatility to turn into a fast commuter bike, on and off-road.</description></family_experience>
<headline>ALL OUT. ANYWHERE.</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Lightweight M4 and A1 frames for stable handling at on-road and off-road speeds</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Geometry is designed for the perfect balance of confidence and speed</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Fast rolling Specialized Trigger 700x38c tyres combine minimal rolling resistance with off-road grip</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Legitimate, reliable off-road capability via double-wall rims and cassette hubs on all bikes</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Custom suspension fork with integrated crown creates sleek downtube design while still utilising standard internal parts; lockout for efficient climbing performance</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>2x10 shifting</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Wide range SRAM WiFLi 10-speed 11-36 rear cassette combined with new 48/32 double chainrings.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Eliminates cross shifting and complexity of a triple chainring but offers equal gear range.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Utilising SRAM 2x10 WiFLi technology combined with a custom 48/32 tooth front crankset.</how1>
<feature2>Integrated Suspension fork</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Custom suspension fork with integrated crown design. Remote lockout function from the handlebar (select models).</what2>
<why2>WHY: Integrated crown design for more integrated front and sleeker, straighter downtube.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Proprietary, custom designed suspension fork crown enables a unique downtube, headtube and fork crown unit. With a lockout, riders gain more efficiency on any surface.</how2>
<feature3>M4 Premium Aluminium frame</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Lightweight, fully butted, smooth welded M4 Premium Aluminium tubing.</what3>
<why3>WHY: M4 aluminium tubing creates the best balance of weight, strength, and compliance.</why3>
<how3>HOW: By controlling everything from the raw material to the extrusion, butting, swaging and heat treatment of the tubes we can optimise our Crosstrail frame for an extreme light and stiff all-road experience.</how3>
<feature4>Internal Cable Routing</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Front and rear derailleur cables are routed inside the frame.</what4>
<why4>WHY: To achieve a sleek look by keeping the bike clutter free, plus to keep gunk out of the cables. It’s a win-win situation!</why4>
<how4>HOW: The cables enter the frame at the top of the downtube and exit at the bottom bracket.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///92E4-11_CT_PRO DISC_BLK RED.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Crosstrail1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Crosstrail2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Crosstrail3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>
