<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14CruX</family_id>
<family_name>CRUX</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>CYCLOCROSS</experience>
<description>The CruX is the weapon of choice for that non-stop, lungs screaming, heart exploding, ‘goashardasyoucanfor60minutes’ cross race. With complete 'cross-dedicated frames (carbon and alloy), in canti and disc, plus race-optimised geometry and tapered SL4-style head tube for nimble handling, it’s everything serious racers look for.</description></family_experience>
<headline>REAL CYCLOCROSS BIKES. FOR RACING.</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Complete ‘cross-dedicated frames—carbon and alloy—in both canti and disc, ready for whatever conditions arise</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Everything serious racers look for-tapered SL4-style head tube for nimble handling, one-piece BB/chainstays. It’s a "Tarmac for the dirt"</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Cross race-specific features, including geometry with low BB and short chainstays, recessed bottle bosses, plus Love Handle and flattened toptube for easy shouldering</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Improved shifting and braking performance in adverse conditions, thanks to internal cable routing with full cable liners and bottom bracket cable guide cover</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>FACT CARBON FRAME, CANTILEVER OR DISC SPECIFIC</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: FACT construction with one-piece, carbon BB chainstay.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Optimises weight and stiffness for greater acceleration, efficiency, and handling.</why1>
<how1>HOW: The one-piece BB/chainstay design resists deflection under extreme pedal loads for improved power transfer.</how1>
<feature2>E5 ALLOY FRAME, CANTILEVER OR DISC SPECIFIC</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: High grade aluminium frame that’s aggressively shaped for the ‘cross racing experience.</what2>
<why2>WHY: Drastically improves the structure of the frame for greater durability and performance.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Each tube is engineered for pure racing, with the best balance of weight and stiffness to maximise performance.</how2>
<feature3>TAPERED HEADTUBE/STEERER TUBE</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Strategically designed headtube/steerer assembly that tapers from 1-1/8” at the top to 1-3/8” at the crown.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Increases strength and stiffness for greater steering precision.</why3>
<how3>HOW: Integrating the 1-3/8” crown with a raised lower bearing adds surface area and strength, which ultimately creates a stiffer junction.</how3>
<feature4>CROSS RACE-SPECIFIC FEATURES</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Frame geometry and features engineered for demands of the ‘cross racing experience.</what4>
<why4>WHY: Cross racing demands a purpose-built machine with race-ready geometry and features to accommodate the nastiest of race conditions.</why4>
<how4>HOW: Shorter chainstays give a sharp and connected ride, recessed bottle bosses, Love Handle, and flattened toptube makes shouldering easier, while full internal cable routing improves shifting in muddy conditions.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///99314-00_CRX_SW CARBON DISC RED_CARB RED WHT.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>
