<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Expedition</family_id>
<family_name>EXPEDITION</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>FITNESS COMFORT</experience>
<description>Unknown territories are quickly discovered in true adventuring style on the Expedition, where comfort is assured and that mile from that B&amp;B to the craft shop on Main Street will seem shorter than ever. With Ground Control Geometry for a more comfortable, upright riding position, plus a more stable ride due to its suspension fork and Body Geometry comfort components, the Expedition is the ultimate in riding comfort.</description></family_experience>
<headline>COMFORTABLY FIT</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Comfortable and confident upright positioning, thanks to Ground Control Geometry</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Ride is always plush and stable due to suspension fork and Body Geometry comfort components</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Miles of stable, worry-free cruising thanks to puncture-resistant 26” tyres</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Accessibility for all riders with low-entry frame options</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Ability to confidently tackle hillier routes, thanks to wide gearing</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>GROUND CONTROL GEOMETRY PLUS LOW-ENTRY MODEL</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Comfortable frame geometry that allows riders to touch their forefoot to the ground when stopped. Low-entry model available.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Provides maximum comfort with minimal back and neck strain, and gives the rider more confidence due to easy access to the ground.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Longer chainstays and a slacker seat tube angle bring the saddle lower to the ground without shortening leg reach, so pedalling remains efficient. Low-entry model features swooping design and is the most accessible in our line, ensuring maximum confidence and stability plus easiest mount/dismount.</how1>
<feature2>SUSPENSION FORK</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Suspension fork with external preload adjustment.</what2>
<why2>WHY: Absorbs bumps on roads and dirt paths, while allowing the rider to dial in the perfect ride feel.</why2>
<how2>HOW: The fork’s coil spring activates when a rider rolls over bumps or rough ground and compresses to absorb the impact. Preload adjustment changes the amount of initial sag in the fork, so suspension can be tuned for individual rider weight.</how2>
<feature3>ADJUSTABLE STEM</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Adjustable alloy stem (Sport model).</what3>
<why3>WHY: Gives rider a large range of adjustment to stem and handlebar angles to dial in optimal position.</why3>
<how3>HOW: By loosening a bolt, the stem can be pivoted to different angles, allowing a greater range of handlebar positions.</how3>
<feature4>COMFORT PLUS SADDLE</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Wide, cruiser-style saddle with dual-density foam and a forgiving spring system.</what4>
<why4>WHY: Provides maximum cushioning and shock absorption, while supporting an upright position for all-day comfort.</why4>
<how4>HOW: The springs act as shock absorbers under the sit bones, while the dual-density foam distributes cushioning and support to the appropriate places.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///82E0-61_EXP_SPORT_BLU WHT SIL.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Expedition1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Expedition2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Expedition3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>