<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Myka</family_id>
<family_name>MYKA</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>RECREATIONAL XC</experience>
<description>The Myka HT is built upon a premium aluminium frame and is the perfect bike for women looking to hone their skills on a value-packed hardtail. Available in both 26-inch and 29er wheel size options and equipped with a tunable suspension fork and reliable disc brakes, the Myka features a low standover height so riders of all sizes will enjoy confident handling and a comfortable fit. Whether the next adventure is a singletrack trail, bike path or fire road, the Myka HT has a durable build that’s engineered for fun.</description></family_experience>
<headline>DISCOVER YOUR ADVENTURE</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Best-in-class value featuring lightweight alloy frame, quality spec package, and women’s Body Geometry contact points</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Stable, confident handling thanks to Recreational XC Geometry with ultra-low standover</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Smoother ride and more control provided by women’s custom-tuned fork suspension</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Reliable, all-weather braking with disc brakes (on all models except base)</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Double-wall rims for lightweight acceleration and durability</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Accessible disc brakes at key model levels</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>WOMEN'S COMPONENTS</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Women’s Body Geometry Riva saddle and women's Myka grips, plus size-specific cranks.</what1>
<why1>WHY: To ensure that female riders get the most comfort, best fit, and efficiency out of every contact point.</why1>
<how1>HOW: We take a systems approach to design, spec’ing each bike individually based on frame size and geometry. Everything from grips to crank arm length are adjusted to riders on each frame size.</how1>
<feature2>CUSTOM-TUNED SUSPENSION</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Alloy forks with custom-tuned, size-specific spring weights.</what2>
<why2>WHY: Creates a more capable, confidence-inspiring ride by delivering the right amount of plushness for the specific rider and helping women utilise all the travel in their fork.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Through extensive field testing, we determine perfect spring weights for female riders. Added features like lockout and hydraulic damping help smooth out bumps and provide more efficiency on smooth terrain.</how2>
<feature3>WOMEN'S A1 PREMIUM ALUMINIUM FRAME</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Lightweight and durable A1 Premium Aluminium frame in dedicated 26-inch and 29-inch models with Women’s Recreational XC Geometry and smaller diameter tubesets. Available in double diamond and step-through versions.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Low standover, lightweight manoeuvrability, and women’s fit give female riders more confidence on the trail so they can achieve all their biking goals. The step-through model adds extra confidence for newer riders.</why3>
<how3>HOW: We optimise the Myka’s geometry and tubesets based on anthropometric data (measures physical variations among women) and the specific needs of the rider to create the best recreational hardtail for women.</how3>
<feature4>ENGINEERING THE BEST-FITTING AND MOST CAPABLE 29ERS FOR WOMEN</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Low standover height is the key to getting on and off the bike with total control. Despite the bigger wheels, we reached our aggressive target of keeping standover height under 695mm for our smallest bike (size 15” is 694mm), and proportionally low for all others, of course.</what4>
<why4>WHY: By using an integrated headset, new flat handlebar, and 80mm-travel fork with female-tuned and size-specific spring rates (accounts for variation in rider weight), we created a low stack height that won’t overwhelm the female rider.</why4>
<how4>HOW: We achieved the shortest possible reach on our 15” bike (378mm), ensuring that every woman, no matter her size, can comfortably reach the handlebars and control the bike.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///81514-42_MYKA HT_ELITE DISC 29_BLK HYP GRN.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///CruX3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>
