<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Rockhopper</family_id>
<family_name>ROCKHOPPER</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>TRAIL HARDTAIL</experience>
<description>Performance, reliability and value—the Rockhopper is designed for stretches of flowing singletrack. With hydraulic disc brakes, 100mm-travel suspension fork and a lightweight fully butted A1 aluminium frame, the Rockhopper delivers proven performance riders will appreciate on the trail.</description></family_experience>
<headline>TRUE TRAIL PERFORMANCE</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Precise handling and efficient power transfer from lightweight and fully butted A1 Premium Aluminium frames with balanced Trail Geometry</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Smoother and more controlled ride with reliable traction in rough conditions due to lightweight, damped suspension forks with lockout</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Maximum confidence, control, and stopping power with hydraulic disc brakes on all models and versatile Specialized Ground Control tyres</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>High durability and low maintenance thanks to quality components, full-cable housings, and corrosion-resistant hardware</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Rockhopper Pro EVO features a longer-travel fork, 15mm thru-axle, and bash guard for optimised descending performance</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>A1 PREMIUM ALUMINIUM FRAME</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Fully formed and butted, lightweight A1 Premium Aluminium frame with balanced Trail 29 Geometry.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Delivers faster acceleration and climbing, remains stable on descents, and offers increased comfort and durability. The combination of forming and butting produces the lightest frame possible, without sacrificing strength.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Fully formed tubes are individually shaped for their unique purpose, allowing our engineers to optimise tubesets for specific performance characteristics. The butting process shaves excess material and weight in low-stress areas of each tube.</how1>
<feature2>HYDRAULIC DISC BRAKES</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: Hydraulic disc brakes equipped on every model.</what2>
<why2>WHY: More consistent stopping power, brake modulation, and overall performance in any weather and all trail conditions.</why2>
<how2>HOW: A master cylinder pumps hydraulic oil to the calliper, which pushes the pistons into contact with the disc rotor. Hydraulic systems produce more power than mechanical brakes, which means increased power at the calliper and more modulation at the lever.</how2>
<feature3>DAMPED 100MM-TRAVEL FORK WITH LOCKOUT</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: 100mm of front suspension travel with lockout.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Riders demand enough travel to handle their favourite trails, but need lockout for extended climbs.</why3>
<how3>HOW: Damped suspension provides a fine-tuned ride with the ability to fully lockout the fork for maximum climbing efficiency. Oil-regulated compression and rebound damping provides a smoother, more controlled ride over rough terrain.</how3>
<feature4>2X10 GEARING</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Pro EVO and Comp models get 2x10 gearing.</what4>
<why4>WHY: Reduced weight and less overlapping gear ratios.</why4>
<how4>HOW: With 10-speed capabilities bikes don’t need triple chainrings, as most ratios are covered with the 20 speeds.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///91214-10_RH_PRO EVO 29_BLK RED.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rockhopper1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rockhopper2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rockhopper3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>