<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Rumor</family_id>
<family_name>RUMOR</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>XC TRAIL</experience>
<description>The Rumor is true, our first women’s full-suspension 29er has arrived. This XC Trail bike will give women the opportunity to head into uncharted singletrack territory. From flowing trails to technical descents, the Rumor is engineered using ground breaking technology to give females the best-fitting, most-capable full-suspension 29er.</description></family_experience>
<headline>TOTAL TRAIL OBSESSION</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Women's XC Trail 29er Geometry and ultra-low standover height for perfect fit and trail performance</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Optimised trail performance with 110mm of custom-tuned suspension keeps the ride quality plush</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>The lightweight, M5 Aluminium 29er frame instills confidence in its trail capability</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>The Rumor’s outstanding component spec makes a lightweight bike that inspires women to challenge themselves on singletrack terrain</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Women’s Body Geometry contact points ensure the perfect fit</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>WOMEN’S SUSPENSION TUNE</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Bike and suspension designed together from the ground up, featuring our custom-tuned spring rates for women.</what1>
<why1>WHY: Delivers a more capable and confidence inspiring bike by keeping the ride quality smooth and tuning spring curves so women can utilise all of their suspension travel.</why1>
<how1>HOW: By designing the bike and suspension in tandem, we can achieve completely balanced performance that’s appropriate to the bike and rider. Extensive field testing and research on women’s centre of gravity and weight distribution helps us determine the optimal spring rates for female riders.</how1>
<feature2>ALL-NEW WOMEN’S M5 ALLOY FRAME</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: All-new design and women's M5 alloy frame featuring Women's XC Trail 29er Geometry and tubesets, 110mm travel, tapered headtube, ultra-low standover height, and full water bottle clearance on all sizes.</what2>
<why2>WHY: To provide the most capable, best fitting women’s full-suspension 29er trail bike.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Designing the bike from the ground up with a two-piece toptube and shock carriage enables us to create in-line suspension and reach our lofty 29er design targets in terms of standover, kinematics, and bottle clearance.</how2>
<feature3>AUTOSAG SUSPENSION TUNING</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: Revolutionary SBC technology, manufactured by FOX, automatically sets the proper sag and air pressure in the shock.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Quick and simple adjustment that guarantees the perfect setting for optimal suspension performance.</why3>
<how3>HOW: In the saddle, the rider pushes a specially designed transfer port on the shock to release air pressure until a set level, based on the rider’s weight. This equalises the positive and negative chambers and achieves perfect sag.</how3>
<feature4>WOMEN’S COMPONENTS</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Women’s Body Geometry Jett saddle, women’s Enduro grips and size-specific components.</what4>
<why4>WHY: To ensure that female riders get the best fit at every contact point.</why4>
<how4>HOW: We take a systems approach to design by spec’ing each bike individually based on frame size and geometry. Everything from small diameter grips to size-specific crank lengths is optimised for females.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///95E2-31_RUMOR_EXPERT 29_CHAR TEAL.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rumor1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rumor2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Rumor3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>