<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Jett</family_id>
<family_name>JETT</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>WOMEN'S XC</experience>
<description>From neighbourhood trails to rolling singletrack, we built the Jett to give riders a capable, comfortable, and versatile hardtail 29er. Equipped with proven XC components and the dialled Women's XC 29er Geometry, Jett riders will enjoy the premium fit, handling, and ride quality of this head-turning ride.</description></family_experience>
<headline>ROLL WITH CONFIDENCE</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>29-inch, trail-smoothing wheels and 27.2mm seat tube take the edge away from rough terrain</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Improved rider confidence with low standover height and Women’s XC 29er Geometry</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Women’s Body Geometry contact points for ultimate fit, comfort, and control</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Greater control and all-weather stopping power with hydraulic disc brakes</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Smoother ride and more control provided by custom-tuned suspension fork</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>2X10 on all models</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>M4 ALLOY FRAME</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: Fully butted and formed, lightweight M4 alloy frame with Women’s XC 29er Geometry.</what1>
<why1>WHY: With smaller sizes and the lowest possible standover height, the M4 Jett frame is built to be the best-fitting women’s hardtail alloy XC 29er frame. Also delivers fast acceleration and climbing, remains stable on descents, and offers increased comfort and durability.</why1>
<how1>HOW: Fully formed tubes are individually shaped for their unique purpose, allowing our engineers to optimise tubesets for specific riding characteristics. Through forming and butting, we are able to produce the lightest frame possible, without sacrificing strength. The Jett frame also features a 27.2mm seatpost for compliance, rack mounts for versatility, and bottle clearance on all frame sizes.</how1>
<feature2>SIZE-SPECIFIC WOMEN'S COMPONENTS</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: All-new women’s Body Geometry Riva saddle and women’s Body Geometry XCT grips, plus frame size-specific rotors, crank lengths and handlebar widths.</what2>
<why2>WHY: To ensure female riders get the most comfort and best possible fit at every contact point on the bike.</why2>
<how2>HOW: By taking a systems approach to designing and spec’ing each bike individually, based on frame size and geometry, to meet the needs of female riders of all sizes. In addition to women’s componentry and touch points, all models include 2X10 for enhanced gearing.</how2>
<feature3>CUSTOM-TUNED SUSPENSION</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: 80mm-travel fork with custom-tuned spring rates. The size small (15”) Jett has a 51mm offset fork crown, while the medium and large frames have a standard 46mm crown offset.</what3>
<why3>WHY: Delivers a more capable and confidence-inspiring ride by keeping the ride quality plush, while keeping ride quality the same regardless of the bike size/fork offset. The size small Jett’s 51mm fork offset maintains the bike’s Women’s XC 29er Geometry, but avoids toe and front tyre clearance issues found on other small 29er frames.</why3>
<how3>HOW: By conducting extensive field testing to study women’s centre of gravity location and weight distribution, we’ve determined the optimal suspension spring rates for female riders and target the perfect rate for each frame size. These spring rates are optimised for female riders to reach full suspension travel over varying terrain. The geometry of each size was optimised for the fork off-set, therefore the small and large-sized frames ride with the same quick and predictable handling.</how3></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///91814-30_JETT_EXPERT 29_BLK FLORED.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Jett1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Jett2.jpg"/>></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>