<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<root>
<bike>
<families>
<family>
<family_id>14Sirrus</family_id>
<family_name>SIRRUS</family_name>
<family_experience><experience>FITNESS COMMUTE</experience>
<description>Ready to roll and dressed to kill, the Sirrus thrives on getting you there fast, and in comfortable style. Its GO! GO! GO! attitude comes courtesy of the road-inspired, lightweight alloy and carbon frames, making it a prime candidate for beat-the-traffic commutes, heart-starting weekend rides, or the event you’ve always dreamed of completing. It’s got all the function of road bike, but with that extra confidence you get from a flat bar. This fit is dialled and ready, right out of the box, so there’s really only one way to ride this versatile beast—flat out.</description></family_experience>
<headline>ROAD HEART. CITY SOUL.</headline>
<rider_benefits><rider_benefit>Greater efficiency and speed thanks to lightweight alloy frame</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Our Body Geometry Fit team worked with engineers to design the Sirrus for comfort and efficiency with ergonomic contact points and Fitness Geometry</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Top performance in wet weather or on mixed terrain without compromising speed on new Specialized Nimbus tyres specifically designed for versatility</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>New FACT 8r carbon frame for ultimate, lightweight, flat bar performance</rider_benefit>
<rider_benefit>Experience-specific drivetrains for all kinds of riders looking to ride on a range of terrains from flat to rolling hills</rider_benefit></rider_benefits>
<why_its_great>WHY IT'S GREAT</why_its_great>
<features><feature1>INNOVATIVE, EXPERIENCE-SPECIFIC DRIVETRAINS</feature1>
<what1>WHAT: High-performing, experience-specific drivetrains that evolve through the line.</what1>
<why1>WHY: To create high-quality, durable drivetrains that provide the most efficient, intuitive, and smoothest experience for the rider at each level–with an emphasis on wide gear ranges.</why1>
<how1>HOW: As you move through the Sirrus line, the experience changes: the gears move with you. The base model accommodates all riders with a triple crankset with a wide gear range for easier climbing, while the top end has 2x10 gearing for ultimate performance.</how1>
<feature2>BODY GEOMETRY TARGA GRIPS AND SADDLES</feature2>
<what2>WHAT: New Body Geometry ergonomic grips and saddles designed to work perfectly with Sirrus.</what2>
<why2>WHY: To optimise comfort at these key contact points, while increasing efficiency in the fitness riding experience.</why2>
<how2>HOW: Ample padding and patented Body Geometry design assure maximum blood flow to sensitive areas, plus hollow Cr-Mo rails for lightweight support and durability. Targa grips use triple-density rubber</how2>
<feature3>FACT 8R CARBON FRAME</feature3>
<what3>WHAT: New FACT 8R carbon frame.</what3>
<why3>WHY: To provide a compliant, comfortable bike to riders looking for road bike speed with flat handlebar fit.</why3>
<how3>HOW: Carbon fibre allows engineers to create a lightweight frame with additional compliance, leading to a fast, confident ride.</how3>
<feature4>DESIGNED WITH BODY GEOMETRY FIT</feature4>
<what4>WHAT: Newly designed, flat bar-specific geometry with lower standover, slacker seat tube angle, and longer reach.</what4>
<why4>WHY: To create the most efficient and comfortable fitness-riding position right out of the box, for a wider range of riders, without major adjustments or swapping components.</why4>
<how4>HOW: Working directly with our Body Geometry Fit professors, we straightened the toptube and made the reach longer. This provides the confidence and stability of a lower standover while allowing the arms and shoulders to loosen in a more ergonomic position on the bars. At the same time we slackened the seat tube to better align the knee over the pedal, increasing efficiency and comfort while pedalling.</how4></features>
<images>
<image href="file:///90914-10_SIR_PRO CARBON DISC_WHT CARB RED.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Sirrus1.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Sirrus2.jpg"/>
<image href="file:///Sirrus3.jpg"/></images>
</family>
</families>
</bike>
</root>